onlinewagestatements.com 2010-11-27

# Privacy Policy

** Skylight Financial Online Privacy and Security Policy:**

At Skylight Financial®, trust has always been the foundation of our relationship with customers. Because you trust us with your financial and personal information, we respect your privacy and take strong action to safeguard that information, including your online sessions. Skylight Financial pledges to protect your privacy online by adhering to the practices described below.

    • Using Information to Help You  
    • Using Information to Help Us  
    • Email  
    • Security of Online Sessions  
    • Preventing Identity Theft  
    • Protecting Children Online  
    • Links to External Sites  
    • External Aggregation Sites

**_Using Information to Help You_**  
To provide you with top service and safeguard your information online, we will need to collect or remember information about you from time to time. In order to complete a transaction, it is necessary to be a customer and to register on the site. During registration, we will ask you to provide us with a Personal ID, Password and Second Factor Authentication. This ensures that when you transact online with us, it will always be safe and secure.

Skylight Financial web sites use temporary session cookies to assist us in securing your online activities and enhance the performance of the site. We examine group activity and do not watch individual browsing patterns.

In addition, we also analyze our visitor trends to help us understand how our customers are using our web site. This enables us to build a more user-friendly experience. While your browser may allow you to "reject" cookies, our Web site requires that you accept all cookies in order for the Web site features and security mechanisms to function fully.

**_Using Information to Help Us_**  
Occasionally, you may encounter banner ads for Skylight Financial products and services on other Internet sites. We may use third party ad serving companies to distribute our ads on sites where we've paid to advertise. When you click on a Skylight Financial banner, it will take you to our site where the advertised product or service is found. Sometimes these ads contain small graphics or tags in them. These tags capture information such as IP address, browser type and pages being viewed when a user clicks on an ad so we can track the effectiveness of our advertising. These tags do not capture personal information about you. The vendors we use to distribute our ads are prohibited from using any information collected except to track advertising effectiveness.

**_Email_**  
We collect and keep the contents of email you send us in addition to your contact address and our response. This enables us to respond to your requests and questions. Email sent to us should be used for inquiries that are not sensitive or confidential as regular, non-encrypted Internet email (the email we use on most of the site) is not secure. If we need information beyond your name, address, email address and phone number, we will provide you with a secure email form. We will never request that you confirm your Personal ID, account numbers, Password or other sensitive information via email.

We will ask for an email address when you set up a new account or service with us. We may use this address to communicate with you regarding our products and services.

**_Security of Online Sessions_**  
We are committed to protecting the confidentiality of your information and online transactions. We use the highest industry standard for online security -- Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption -- to secure your online sessions. This process safeguards your banking session from intruders.

**_Preventing Identity Theft_**  
Skylight Financial is dedicated to protecting your personal information. Strict policies and procedures have been implemented to ensure that your personal information is kept confidential. Only authorized signers can access account information. Every effort is made to protect our customers from fraud. We will never initiate a request for sensitive information from you via email (i.e., Social Security Number, Personal ID, Password, PIN or account number). If you receive an email that requests this type of sensitive information, you should be suspicious of it. We strongly suggest that you do not share your Personal ID, Password, PIN or account number with anyone, under any circumstances. If you receive a suspicious looking email, please forward it to contact@skylight.net or call our Customer Care Center toll-free at 1-800-686-3363.

Learn more about email fraud and how to protect yourself from identity theft.

**_Protecting Children Online_**  
Skylight Financial feels that it is extremely important to guard the identity and privacy of children, and we encourage parents to supervise their children's interactions online. We do not intentionally market to or solicit personal information from children under the age of 13. In the event that we receive personal information from a child whom we know to be under 13, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child or seek parental consent. For more information or to review information a child may have provided, call Skylight Financial Customer Service. For more information on the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), you can visit the Federal Trade Commission site at 

**_Links to External Sites_**  
At times, we may provide links to sites outside the control of Skylight Financial to alert you to products, information and services offered by third parties. Provided links are meant to supplement Skylight Financial products, services or information or provide other information we believe may be of interest to you. Although we will only provide links to sites we believe are reputable, we do not make any representations concerning the linked sites' contents or availability. Please note that linked sites may have different privacy and information security policies than Skylight Financial. You should review each site's privacy and information security policies carefully before you enter confidential information onto the site.

**_External Aggregation Sites_**  
Please use caution when using external financial aggregation or consolidation services. Financial aggregation and consolidation services collect your personal information from a variety of sources on one site. For example, they could collect your checking and savings account balances at your bank, the value of your stocks and bonds in your brokerage account and your frequent flier mileage information from an airline. Financial aggregators do this by having you provide them with your identification information and password for each individual Web site, and then using these passwords to access each account. You must provide your permission and information to allow these services to collect this data. **Never provide your account information or password to a site that you do not recognize and fully trust.**

_You should know: You will be unable to contest the validity of any Skylight Financial transaction initiated by a consolidation site using access information you provide_ , whether or not you were aware of the specific transaction. You may revoke an aggregator's authority to access your account only by notifying us, in which case we may need to block your account until we issue new access codes.

*By clicking on this link, you will leave skylight.net. Skylight Financial is not responsible for the content of our products and services provided by this site nor does it guarantee the accuracy of information contained in this site. The link will direct you to another Internet site containing information that may be useful to you. This site is not controlled or endorsed by Skylight Financial.
